{
    "subject": "resource/Horse_Soldier!_Horse_Soldier!",
    "predicate": "ontology/recordLabel",
    "object": "resource/Stony_Plain_Records",
    "human_readable": "Horse Soldier!'s album is released by Stony Plain Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9765452742576599,
            "question": "Are there any other albums released by Stony Plain Records besides 'Horse Soldier!'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9200754165649414,
            "question": "Who released the album 'Horse Soldier!'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.906337320804596,
            "question": "Is 'Horse Soldier!' a newly released album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.869009256362915,
            "question": "When was the album 'Horse Soldier!' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8637285828590393,
            "question": "Which record label is associated with the album 'Horse Soldier!'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8590025305747986,
            "question": "What is the name of the album released by Stony Plain Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8058878779411316,
            "question": "Name a musical album released by Stony Plain Records."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6515740156173706,
            "question": "What is the popularity of the album 'Horse Soldier!'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46874678134918213,
            "question": "What genre of music is likely featured on 'Horse Soldier!'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3953624963760376,
            "question": "Does Stony Plain Records specialize in a particular music genre?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Horse Soldier!'s album is released by Stony Plain Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3487_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is likely featured on 'Horse Soldier!'",
            "html": "dbpedia_3487_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the popularity of the album 'Horse Soldier!'",
            "html": "dbpedia_3487_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a musical album released by Stony Plain Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3487_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3487_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3487_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3487_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3487_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3487_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3487_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3487_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3487_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3487_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3487_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document mentions that \"Horse Soldier!  Horse Soldier!\" was included in a list of albums that helped define Stony Plain Records, indicating it was indeed released by Stony Plain Records."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}